<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">COVID-19 Status</string>
    <string name="home">Stats</string>
    <string name="home_toolbar">COVID-19 Statistics</string>
    <string name="countries">Countries</string>
    <string name="safety">Safety</string>

    <string name="total_cases">Total Cases</string>
    <string name="total_deaths">Total Deaths</string>
    <string name="total_recovered">Total Recovered</string>
    <string name="country_detail">Country Detail</string>
    <string name="active_cases">Active Cases</string>

    <string name="app_club_link">Copyright © 2020 <a href="http://appclub.tech/">APP CLUB</a>\nData Source - https://corona.lmao.ninja
    </string>
    <string name="country_flag">Country Flag</string>
    <string name="cases_today">Cases Today</string>
    <string name="deaths_today">Deaths Today</string>

    <string name="title_safety_fragment">Safety Center</string>
    <string name="refresh_status">Refresh Status</string>
    <string name="navigation_information">Navigation Information</string>
    <string name="stats_desc">Statistics tab contains information on the global count.
         Either swipe to refresh the statistics or use the icon in the top right corner.
    </string>
    <string name="countries_desc">
        Countries tab contains a list of every country. Select a country for detailed information.
    </string>
    <string name="safety_center_desc">Safety tab is the safety center where precautions from COVID-19 are mentioned. As this application
        is developed in Pakistan, we have provided the official website and helpline for Pakistan only.
    </string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="visit_pakistan_official_covid_19_website">Visit Pakistan Official COVID-19 Website</string>
    <string name="call_helpline_1166">Call helpline (1166) - Pakistan</string>
    <string name="safety_tips">Safety Tips</string>

    <string name="safety_desc">A list of precautions which should be taken against COVID-19 as there isn\'t
        a vaccine available yet. Ensure following steps are being taken to keep yourself and others out of risk.
    </string>

    <string name="tips_image">Safety Tips Placeholder</string>

    <!-- Hand Wash -->
    <string name="hand_wash_title">Wash your hands</string>
    <string name="hand_wash_description">Wash your hands for 20 seconds using an Anti-bacterial soap or hand wash.
         If outside, carry a sanitizer. Do not greet anyone when visiting anywhere. Follow Social Distancing for time-being for keeping
        yourself and others out of risk
    </string>

    <!-- Medical Mask -->
    <string name="medical_mask_title">Use a medical mask</string>
    <string name="medical_mask_description">Use a medical mask whenever going outside or if you are facing the symptoms
        of COVID-19. If you have Flu, are frequently sneezing or going through a fever, use a mask so it does not effect others
    </string>

    <!-- Social Distancing -->
    <string name="social_distancing_title">Understand Social Distancing</string>
    <string name="social_distancing_description">Avoid any kind of gathering, stay at least 3ft away from everyone.
         Don\'t roam outside due to unnecessary means. Keep yourself clean and avoid any kind of physical contact.
    </string>

    <!-- Stay Home -->
    <string name="stay_home_title">Stay at Home</string>
    <string name="stay_home_description">Stay inside your homes. Your home is your fortress against COVID-19.
         Avoid going outside due to unnecessary reasons. Work from home if possible and if not then take every possible
         precaution like medical mask, sanitizer, and gloves.
    </string>

    <!-- Fruits & Vegetables -->
    <string name="fruits_veges_title">Consume Fruits &amp; Vegetables</string>
    <string name="fruits_veges_description">Fruits &amp; vegetables make your immune system strong, as COVID-19 can be defeated
         with a strong immune system. Eat, Share, Advise Fruits &amp; Vegetables everyday to make your immune system
         a powerful shield against COVID-19.
    </string>

    <!-- Kindess -->
    <string name="kindness_title">Be Kind</string>
    <string name="kindness_description">Be Kind to everyone as much as possible in this time of need.
        Help others as per their requirements. Take care of your elderly, love them, respect them and
        motivate them.
    </string>
    <string name="statistics">Statistics</string>

</resources>
